pinterestplugin.com 2018-12-21

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy ("Policy") describes how we collect, protect and use the personally
identifiable information ("Personal Information") you ("User", "you" or "your") provide on
the http://www.plafortnite.online website and any of its products or services
(collectively, "Website" or "Services"). It also describes the choices available to you
regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update
this information. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do
not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.
Collection of personal information
We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you fill any
online forms on the Website. You can choose not to provide us with certain information,
but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Website's features.
Collection of non-personal information
When you visit the Website our servers automatically record information that your
browser sends. This data may include information such as your computer's IP address,
browser type and version, operating system type and version, language preferences or
the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website
that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our
Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.
Use of collected information
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience;
improve our website; improve customer service and respond to queries and emails of
our customers; run and operate our Website and Services. Non-personal information
collected is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical
information regarding Website traffic and usage. This statistical information is not
otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the
system.
Children
We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of
13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information
through our Website or Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor
their children's Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their
children never to provide personal information through our Website or Service without
their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has
provided personal information to us through our Website or Service, please contact us.
Cookies
The Website uses "cookies" to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a
text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used
to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to
you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
We may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for statistical purposes to
operate our Website and Services. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your

browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you
may not be able to fully experience the features of the Website and Services.
Advertisement
We may display online advertisements and we may share aggregated and non-
identifying information about our customers that we collect through the registration
process or through online surveys and promotions with certain advertisers. We do not
share personally identifiable information about individual customers with advertisers. In
some instances, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver
tailored advertisements to the intended audience.
Links to other websites
Our Website contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us.
Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other
websites or third parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website
and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that may collect personal
information.
Information security
We secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure
environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain
reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect
against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of personal information
in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless
network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal
information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the
Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and
all information and data exchanged between you and our Website cannot be
guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in
transit by a third party, despite best efforts.
Data breach
In the event we become aware that the security of the Website has been compromised
or users Personal Information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result
of external activity, including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve the
right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but not limited to,
investigation and reporting, as well as notification to and cooperation with law
enforcement authorities. In the event of a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts
to notify affected individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the
user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law. When we do we
will post a notice on the Website.
Changes and amendments
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy relating to the Website or Services at
any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this privacy policy on the
Website. When we do we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.
Continued use of the Website after any such changes shall constitute your consent to
such changes.

Acceptance of this policy
You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and
conditions. By using the Website or its Services you agree to be bound by this Policy. If
you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to use or
access the Website and its Services.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us.
This document was last updated on September 12, 2017
